Tyshanae Thompson

Fort Worth, TX• 817-630-1920 • Dtyshanae@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tyshanae-thompson-536700204

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A hardworking individual who has gained knowledge with Microsoft Excel, Word, PowerPoint, and QuickBooks. Positive and outgoing team player with integrity and a record of being very punctual. I am analytical, organized and detail-oriented with over 6 years of customer service experience. Seeking a position that will allow me to utilize my skills such as critical thinking, teamwork, and programming.

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Strong Interpersonal Skills
- Great Communication Skills
- Financial Analysis
- Excellent Math Comprehension
- Understanding of Generally Accepted Accounting Principles
- Excel Formulas

- Pivot Tables
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- HTML
- CSSReact
- Bootstrap

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCE

Springboard Bootcamp

February 2023-Current

Software Development Career Program

- Hands on experience with a 1:1 industry export mentor oversight, and completion of multiple portfolio projects.
- 9-month intensive course in Front-End Development using ReactJS and the development of proficiency with data structures and algorithms and object-oriented programming.
- Programming, problem solving skills ability to break down a problem into its component pieces, think through it logically, and come up with a solution.

Aston Carter August 2022 – Current

Accounts Receivable Analyst (Contractor)

- Supports the A/R team by posting collections to the A/R system daily. This includes researching past due invoices and any discrepancies in payments and keeping and maintaining A/R files for back-ups and research
- Recorded \$300,000+ monthly in collections received from customers in DCMS.
- Strengthen vendors and customer relations regarding logistics by communicating via email or phone.
- File and Maintain Daily Collection journal reports/check copies.

Express Employment: Fort Worth, Tx

May 2022-August 2022

Accounting Associate (Contractor)

- Perform bookkeeping services for multiple complex clients or clients in transition. This includes both forprofit and not-for-profit entities.
- Streamlined preparation and review of financial reports, profit and loss statements, and balance sheets on a (monthly and yearly basis), saving 25 hours monthly.
- Monitor revenue and expense accounts through quick books online. This included performing bank reconciliations of a total of assets worth \$10M+.
- Strengthen client relationships by communicating regularly and building trustworthy relationships.

Robert Half: Arlington, TX

November 2021-May 2022

Accounts Receivable Clerk (Temporary)

- Processes daily invoices/credit, apply cash receipts, and help with the collection of past-due balances.
- Prepare statements and reports that require the utilization of a variety of sources.

- Prepare correction documents as required.
- Handle administrative needs of the AP department.
- Verify log and send checks.
- Provide internal and external audit assistance as needed.

EDUCATION

Springboard Bootcamp

Software Development Career Program

Completed Projects-

- Memory Game (JavaScript, Html, CSS). Using my knowledge of DOM manipulation and timers to build a sophisticated browser-based memory game.
- Fruit Search (JavaScript, Html, CSS). Extensively used DOM manipulation, advanced array methods, and the features of ES2015. This is a small predictive text search app for fruit.
- Loan Payment Calculator (JavaScript, Html, CSS). Created a loan testing calculator app that would calculate monthly payments. The calculator takes an amount to loan (the principle), a term in years, and a yearly rate. The output returned is the monthly payment of the loan.
- Meme Generator (JavaScript, Html, CSS). Generated memes from any image file uploaded and any text of choice. Using my knowledge of web fundamentals and DOM manipulation.
- Hack or Snooze (JavaScript, Html, CSS) Functional clone of Hacker News based on the data available in their API. It will allow users to create accounts and log in, save their favorite articles, and upload stories of their own. Using AJAX and jQuery.

Southern New Hampshire University: Manchester, NH

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration – Accounting (BBA)